Guide to the Marguerite Young Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2000 Acquisition, circa 1940-1994; Series III; 45; (46 boxes)
  - Notebooks, 6 (Box 78)
  - Writing drafts, 4 (Box 78)
  - Writing drafts, 10 (Box 79)
  - Writing drafts of "The Riley manuscript", 3 (Box 79)
  - Writing drafts of "The Riley manuscript", 2 (Box 80)
  - Photographs, 10 (Box 80)
  - Printed artwork (Box 80)
  - Bracelet (Box 80)
  - Blank checks, 2 (Box 80)
  - Printed material, 2 (Box 80)
  - Realia (Box 81)
  - Realia (Box 82)
  - Audiocassettes of Miss Macintosh, My Darling readings for WBAI-FM Pacifica Radio, 1974-1975
    - Ruth Ford, Chap[ter] 8, Part II, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979444)
    - Michael Wager 3 and 4, Chap[ter] 29, Part I, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979451)
    - Anais Nin Introduction - Miss MacIntosh, Interview with Marguerite Young, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979469)
    - Marian Seldes reads chapter two, pt. I, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979477)
    - Marian Seldes, ch[apter] 79, pt. 2, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979485)
    - Marian Seldes reads the concl[usion] of chap[ter] two, undated; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979493)
  - Audiocassette of "Lecture Women's Coffee Hour Susan B. Anthony birthday by Marguerite Young", 1978; 1 (Box 83, Item barcode 39002109979501)
  - Two drawings by Leola Bergmann entitled "Miss MacIntosh, our darling! For Marguerite- 11/89", 1989 November (Box 86)
- August 2000 Acquisition, 1999; Series IV; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  Contains bound and galley proofs of Young's Harp Song for a Radical: The Life and Times of Eugene Victor Debs.
  Formerly classified as Uncat MSS 52.
  Donated by Charles Ruas, 2000.
  - Harp Song for a Radical: The Life and Times of Eugene Victor Debs, bound proofs, 1999; 3 (Box 84)
  - Harp Song for a Radical: The Life and Times of Eugene Victor Debs, galley proofs, 1999; 4 (Box 85)